{
  "translations": {
    "en": {
      "q1": {
        "type": "select",
        "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
        "question":"Which of the following are  alphabet sets?",
        "answer": ["{$a$, $b$, $c$}", "{0, 1}", "{?, $a$, $x$}"],
        "choices": ["{$a$, $b$, $c$}", "{0, 1}","$A$" ,"{?, $a$, $x$}"]
      },
      "q2": {
        "type": "textBox",
        "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
        "question":" Which of these are terminals, and which are non-terminals?",
        "answer": ""
        
      },
      "q2_2":{
        "type": "textBox",
        "question":"What are the variables in the given grammar?",
        "answer": "<noun>",
        "choices": ["<sentence>", "<subject>", "<verb>", "<d.o.>", "<article>", "<noun>", "a", "the", "Fritz", "ran", "ate"]
      },
      "q3": {
        "type": "select",
        "question":"What are the terminals in the given grammar?",
        "answer":  ["a", "the", "Fritz", "ran", "ate"],
        "choices": ["<sentence>", "<subject>", "<verb>", "<d.o.>", "<article>", "<noun>", "a", "the", "Fritz", "ran", "ate" ]
      },
      "q4":{
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"The <d.o> variable has two productions associated with it. Write one.",
        "answer": ["<article><noun>", "<noun>"],
        "choices": ["<article><noun>", "<noun>"]
      },
      "q5":{
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"Which variable we must start with?",
        "answer": "<sentence>",
        "choices": ["<sentence>", "<subject>", "<verb>", "<d.o.>", "<article>", "<noun>"]
      },
      "q6":{
        "type": "textBox",
        "question":"What is the substitute for <subject> variable?",
        "answer": "<noun>"
      },
      "q7":{
        "type": "textBox",
        "question": "What is the substitute for <noun>?",
        "answer":"t"
      },
      "q8":{
        "type": "textBox",
        "question":"What is the substitute for <verb>?",
        "answer": "hit"
      },
      "q9":{
        "type": "textBox",
        "question":"What is the substitute for <d.o>??",
        "answer":"<article><noun>"
      },
      "q10":{
        "type": "textBox",
        "question":"What is the substitute for <article>?",
        "answer":"the"
      },
      "q11":{
        "type": "textBox",
        "question":"What is the substitute for <noun>?",
        "answer":"ball"
      },
      "q12":{
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"Can we derive these sentences?  The ball hit Fritz, or The ball ate the ball",
        "answer":"Yes",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q13":{
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"Do grammars provide sentences with correct semantics (meaning)?",
        "answer":"Yes",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q14":{
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"What does x represent?",
        "answer":"Variables",
        "choices": ["Variables", "Terminals"]

      },
      "q15":{
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"What does y represent?",
        "answer":["Variables", "Terminals"],
        "choices": ["Variables", "Terminals"]
      },
      "q16":{
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"What is ?",
        "answer":[" " ],
        "choices": [" "]
      },
      "q17":{
        "type": "textBox",
        "question":"What states can be combined?",
        "answer":"{abc,abbc,abbcc,bcc,bcbc,bcbcc,abac,ababc,ababcc}"
      },
      "q18":{
        "type": "multiple",
        "question":"Let //sigma={$a$,$b$}, $L1$={$ab$,$aba$}, What is $L0$?",
        "answer": ["{$λ$}"],
        "choices": ["{$λ$}", "{}<Empty set>", "$λ$"]
      },
      "q19":{
        "type": "textBox",
        "question":"Let //sigma={$a$,$b4}, $L1$={$ab$,$aba$}, What is $L2$? ",
        "answer": "{abab, ababa, abaab, abaaba}"
      },
      "q19_1":{
        "type": "textBox",
        "question":"Let //sigma={$a$,$b$}, $L1$={$ab$,$aba$}, What is $L3$?",
        "answer": "{ababab, ababaab, abaabab, abaabaab, abababa, ababaaba, abaababa, abaabaaba}"
      }
    }
  }
}

